



ABOUT ME

My background is in Art and Design which led me to work in the screen printing industry for many years. Now I'm starting on a new adventure in the web development field. I've always enjoyed challenges and troubleshooting so I knew I'd be a great programmer. I'm a fast learner that easily adapts to new situations. I'm Proficient in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, and React.js., Node.js, Express and MySQL.



CONTACT

813.391.1719

nickablack@gmail.com



SOCIAL MEDIA

github.com/nblack0917

linkedin.com/in/nick-a-black



DISC GOLE

SALES

EXPERIENCE

HTML CSS **JAVASCRIPT** REACT.JS **EXPRESS.JS PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR**

NICK BLACK

WEB DEVELOPER



WORK HISTORY

Zollege

March 2021 - Present

Junior Web Developer: Collaborating with a small team to develop and deploy small applications for a non-profit sector of Zollege and Austin Coding Academy.

Flint Avenue Marketing

Junior Web Developer: Collaborating with other developers to create, maintain, or debug web and mobile applications. Primarily focusing on React.JS and React Native.

River City Supply, LLC

January 2017 - March 2020

Sales associate and service specialist: Performed sales (counter, phone, and online), inventory and warehouse management, ordering, and customer service. Also a Mimaki certified wide-format printer service technician.



EDUCATION

Austin Coding Academy

September 2020 - March 2021

Full Stack Web Developer Certificate: Learned the most popular and common programming languages and how to build a site or app from idea to deployment.

Ringling College of Art and Design

August 1999 - May 2003

Bachelors of Fine Arts majoring in Illustration: Learned multiple drawing, painting, and sculpting techniques from industry professionals. Graduated with High Honors.



CURRENT PROJECTS



REFERENCES

River City Supply, LLC

Personal Portfolio

- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- · Showcases a handful of projects
- · https://nblack0917.github.io/nickBlackwebdev-portfolio/
- Garden-plan-ter
 - · React.js, Express.js, MySQL
 - · Garden Layout and Scheduling app
 - · https://garden-plan-ter.netlify.app/
- O Draftrr.com
 - · React.js, Express.js, MySQL
 - · First draft writing app
 - · https://draftrr.com/



512.454.0505 Keith Kritselis

Kevin Wilson

Austin Coding Academy Instructor / Project Manager keith@zollege.com 512. 947.9248

kevin@ScreenPrintSupplies.com



HOBBIES















- I grew up next door to an actor from The Sopranos
- My artwork has been displayed in a gallery show that also featured Shepard Fairey's art